Building applications has gone a lot
easier thanks to AI. But let's be
honest, when I say applications, I
really mean prototypes. There's not that
much quality that's shipped. Whenever
you see someone vibe code an app, the
moment they have 10 users, that app
crashes. And that's because they don't
know how to design a system. And that's
the same reason why a developer who uses
AI will build a more robust app compared
to someone who's not a developer. But
that's what today's video is going to
help with. I'm going to show you how to
design a robust system when a gentic
engineering when you're building your
applications with AI. And the way I'm
going to do it is I'm going to explain
to you how my app Pluto was built from
the ground up. All the tools that I use,
the tech stack that I use, the info that
I use, the decisions I made, how the
code is structured, how I use AI. I'm
literally going to cover everything. If
you have plans on building an app that's
going to go to production that people
are going to be using, you're going to
need to watch this video. I'm going to
leave no stone unturned. This might be
20 minutes, 30 minutes, however long
this video is. Let's get straight into
it. So, building robust applications
with AI. First and foremost, what does
system design mean? And I'm going to
more so focus in this age of AI. The
simple definition of system design, the
fancy definition is it's a process of
planning the architecture, components,
modules, interfaces, and data flow of
the software system to satisfy specific
requirements. In the old days preai, we
used to watch a lot of videos like this
to learn how to design systems, right?
You had to figure out what you're going
to use for storage, where you're going
to place your load balancer, what
service you're going to use for alerts,
what your CI/CD pipeline look like. All
this stuff was something that a system
designer has to think about. But in this
current age of AI, there are a lot of
tools that abstract this that make it a
lot easier for us to implement these
things in our system. Now, one thing you
need to realize about designing a system
is in engineering, whether you're an
engineer or not, one thing you need to
understand is engineering is all about
trade-offs. Meaning, there is no such
thing as a perfect system. There is no
such thing as this system handles every
scenario, every case. Everything has
trade-offs. Every stack has trade-offs.
Every tool you use has trade-offs. Every
info provider you use has trade-offs.
Nothing is perfect except Jesus. So,
understanding this, when designing our
system, there's a couple things we need
to think about. First, the is
scalability. The system's ability to
handle growing amount of traffic or data
by adding resources. Meaning, if your
app starts to get bombarded, is your
system designed in a way where all you
have to do is go to some dashboard, add
some servers, and then you're good to
go. Or does it autoscale? Reliability.
What is the chance of your system going
down? Is the provider you're using known
to go down always? That's a decision we
have to take into consideration.
Performance, does this allow your app to
be fast? Right? We need our apps to be
zooming fast. If the tool that we're
using or the way we've architected the
app is slow, that's something we need to
think about. And last but not least is
the money. Is this going to cost us an
arm and a leg? Can we only afford an arm
or can we afford an arm and a leg or can
we afford nothing? These are things we
need to think about. Engineering is all
about trade-offs. Before we get into
Pluto system design, I want to kind of
give you a breakdown of all the info
available and how all these things work.
In the old days, the way websites and
apps would be served is companies had
their own servers. They had their own
metal. They had server racks in their
office. There was an couple of IT nerds.
There was a couple of, you know,
computer programmers. There's a couple
of DevOps people. And you are basically
scaling the website yourself. So, if you
have a lot of traffic and you don't have
the hardware to support you, you are
cooked. If you have all these server
racks and you don't have traffic, you
just wasted a bunch of money. So, it was
a time where you had to be very
calculated. It's very expensive. It's
hard to predict and it's not easy to
scale up. Then companies like Amazon,
uh, Google and Microsoft built their own
cloud providers, right? Amazon built
AWS, Google built GCP, Microsoft built
Azure, and then you have Cloudflare. And
these guys basically bought their own
metal, placed it in different areas, and
they're like, we will be the provider
where you can run your apps, right? And
what was cool about AWS and GCP and
Azure is that I didn't have to manage my
own server racks anymore. I didn't need
IT guys on the floor plugging in stuff.
I can just deploy my application
straight to AWS, straight to Azure. They
have all these different services and
tools, right, that are all managed by
them. And they handle the nitty-gritty
and heavy stuff. And this is when the
web exploded. This is when sites
exploded, backends exploded. A lot of
cool stuff started to show up in the
web. And this is also what we call an
abstraction. Now, you might feel like
these are all big engineering terms. If
you want to build something cool, lock
in and listen. Abstraction in computer
science is the process of hiding complex
implementation details and focusing only
on essential highle features of an
object or system. So they basically AWS,
GCP and Azure and cloud for they
basically abstracted the need for me to
have a physical server, the need for me
to set up software to run stuff on the
physical server. They took care of that.
And then as time went on, another layer
of abstraction popped up, right? And you
have Convex, you have Versel, you have
Superbase, you have Neon and all these
different companies. Now just, you know,
if any of the employees from the
companies watch, yes, Versel for example
does have their own metal. I I I think
so does Planet Scale, but just
hypothetically, Verscell when they
started wrapped AWS, GCP or one of these
guys, right? Convex wrapped, same thing,
right? So this level abstraction made it
a lot easier to use these tools which
made it a lot easier to use this right
because I don't know if many of you have
used AWS. AWS is pretty fine. I don't
know if many of you have used GCP or
Azure. I have an Azure certificate.
Azure is terrible to use. GCP is
terrible to use. I don't even know
anyone who knows how to deploy React app
on Azure in under 5 minutes. It's that
messed up and all over the place. So you
have tools and info providers like
convex, versel, superbase and all these
other companies that basically wrap or
abstract AWS, GCP, Azure and Cloudflare.
The reason why I say this, this layer of
infrastructure has essentially made it
easy for you and me to build our
applications. I don't deploy on AWS,
GCP, Azure. Uh sometimes I use
Cloudflare, but for the most part I use
Verscell. For my back end, I use convex.
If I need a Postgress database, I'm
going to use planet scale. I no longer
have to go this level down the
abstraction path, nor do I have to go
this level down. Now, you might be like,
why are you explaining this to me? I'm
trying to enic engineer because when I
talk about Pluto's system design, all
this stuff is going to help it make
sense. And to just give you a breakdown
of how things are today, you still have
people who use their own metal, don't
recommend. You have things that are
built. You have companies that provide
this service for you like the AWS's, the
GCPs, these things are very powerful.
But the developer experience or should I
say the agent experience sucks and then
you have tools like convex forcell and
all these other companies that have
amazing developer experience can easily
scale up. They do a lot of the hard work
for you that you and I don't need to
worry about. Yo yo, wake up.
>> You can't be sleeping on the job. Who's
going to review the code?
I hate code review, but it has to get
done. And that's why I love Gretile.
See, I have a huge PR here on an open
source project I have called Ralphie.
Over 4,341
lines done by this contributor. Now,
this is a lot of lines of code, and I'm
probably going to miss something, but
the way I use Gravile in my code reviews
as follows. I have a Gravile review
that's run on this PR. Mind you, this is
a pretty large PR. And what I love about
Gravile is the summary it gives me plus
the confidence score. The confidence
score tells me whether this is worth my
time reviewing or not. Anything below a
four out of five is something I'm not
going to personally review. Imagine
spending all that time only to find out
this PR still requires work. But with
Gravile, all I need to do is read the
summary, review the confidence score. If
it's under a four out of five, it's not
worth merging. Doing this has allowed me
and my team to ship at warp speed. So,
make sure to check out Greile. The link
is in the description down below, or you
can go to rosmike.link/greptile.
They have a two-eek free trial and it's
pretty generous. So, take advantage of
it. Believe me, once you start using it,
you won't want to stop. Check them out.
The link is down in the description
below. So, let's talk about Pluto. So,
when building Pluto, there's a couple
things that are pretty interesting.
First and foremost, with Pluto, I needed
OOTH that businesses could use, right? I
needed the big boy OOTH. I needed people
who maybe want sock two compliance and
all these other things, right? So, O is
something I had to think about. And then
I know there might be people who are
using this for personal use, but there
also might be businesses. And if
businesses want to use this, maybe it's
a manager who's setting this up. And
then the manager invites the employees
of the company and then they set it up.
And then I have to think about billing,
right? What kind of billing do I want?
Do I want a subscription? People already
pay for subscriptions and I think people
are tired of subscriptions. Maybe we can
do a credit based system where you can
just top up and use as you go. So then
you have to build that out as well.
Another thing is again, this is an
agent, right? So, I need to think about
where I'm going to deploy this agent.
The place I deploy needs to be sort of
affordable, but it also needs to be able
to scale and needs to not go down. It
needs to be something that's reliable.
So, these are all the things I had to
think about when initially planning out
Pluto. Now, let's talk about Pluto.
Pluto has four client surfaces, right?
There's a web app, there's a desktop
app, there's a mobile app. Well, the
mobile app was just one fable run, and
then there's an admin site, right? Like
an internal admin site. Now, when you're
building your app, you got to think of a
couple things. You got to think of the
client, the server, and the database.
The client is basically the place where
people interact with your app. So, this
could be your website, your mobile app,
or your desktop app. Now, it's important
to pick the tool you're familiar with.
And in this case, for my web apps, I use
spelt kit. So, spelt kit is basically
the nex.js for spelt. I love Spelkit. A
I love Spelkit. It's very minimal. It's
fast. It's easy to build performance
sites with it. So, I'm using Spelkit for
the client. But here's the thing. What
if I wanted a mobile app, right? If I
wanted a mobile app, I can build a
native Mac OS app. But let's say I want
an Android app as well. Expo Plus React
Native for the mobile app, right? And
let's say I want a desktop app. And then
for the desktop app, I'm going to use
Electron. And I'm just going to wrap the
website. Right? This is these are things
that I can do with Electron. Now I have
a web app, I have a mobile app, and then
I have a desktop app. Like am I going to
have like three different projects with
three different repos? Like how am I
going to manage this? Let me introduce
you to our good friend called a mono
repo. A monorreo is basically one giant
repository of code where multiple
different pieces of your application can
live. Right? So I can have my web app in
one repo. I can have my mobile app in
one repo. I can have my desktop in one
repo. And I can also have my backend,
right? That all these different
services, right? The desktop app
communicates with the backend, the
mobile app communicates with the
backend, and the web app communicates
with the back end. The reason why a
monor repo is cool or having all this in
one codebase is cool is because when I'm
using my agent, when I'm using my AI of
choice, in this case Fable 5, it's
finally back. When I'm using Fable 5 or
whatever model of choice, Fable 5, the
agent has access to the entire codebase
even though I have a web app, a desktop
app, a mobile app, right? If I have like
a web app, a separate repository for the
web app, a separate repository for the
mobile app, a separate repository for
the desktop app, then there's all these
separated contexts, it's very hard for
me, the human to manage. And you might
be someone who doesn't really know how
to code. Good luck. It's going to be a
tough time. So whenever I initialize my
applications, whenever I start my
application, I almost always start with
a monor repo. And in this case, because
I use Verscell to deploy, I use Turbo
Repo. And this is how I architect my
apps, right? So I always start with a
monor repo. The reason I start with a
monor repo is it allows me to have, you
know, multiple different clients, one
unified backend. I can even have one
component library, one UI library, and
it be shared with all these different
client services, right? And in terms of
what I use for my web app, I told you I
use Felt. for mobile, unless I don't
need an Android app. I usually I like to
go Swift, but I'm going to use Expo and
React Native. And then I'm using
Electron for the desktop app. But now I
have to think about my server and my
database. And by the way, if you feel
like this is a lot of information, I'm
literally going to put this all of this
together. So just listen and take notes.
When it comes to my server and database
and particularly my server or my
backend, there's a couple things I need
to think about. My server is going to
allow me to read data from my database.
My server is going to allow me to write
data to my database. My server is going
to allow me to interact with external
services, right? Like make an API call
to like a a weather API, right? And
there's a couple things I also want. I
want to make sure these don't fail and
these aren't slow. Now, here's the
thing. One thing that I want you to know
is you should never ever ever ever ever
ever read data from the client directly
to the database. The client should never
ever ever ever talk to the database. And
this is one of the biggest reasons why
why I'm not a fan of Superbase. Now,
Superbase does have a server library, so
you can not do this, but most people do
this and then they set up RLS. And to
me, that's just a fool's game. Real
system should work as follows. The
client calls the server. The server
calls the database. The database
responds to the server. And then the
server tells the client. This is secure.
But if I have my client talking to my
database, what basically someone can do
is they can inspect element, go to the
network tab, see the networks, read your
API key, and then you're cooked. You're
absolutely cooked. So when I am
designing my backend, I need my backend
to do all these things, but I also need
to make sure my backend communicates
with my database. In the old days, you
would have or not in the old days, I
mean people still do it now. You can
have a NodeJS backend and then you have
a Postgress DB, right? You would build
this and then build this and have these
communicate. Remember when I told you
there are abstractions that make things
easier, right? Back in the day, I would
have to deploy my Node.js app, a backend
on AWS, and then I would have to set up
an AWS Postgress instance or I could use
GCP, whatever it is, and then I'd have
those two communicate. But then we have
an abstraction layer above AWS called
Convex. And Convex is a beautiful thing.
Why is Convex a beautiful thing? Convex
takes my server, right, my back end, and
marries it to my database. And what I
mean by marries it, let me use better
language. I basically get both of them
in one box. So I get a backend. I think
a backend is better here, where I can
read data from the DB, write data to the
to my DB, interact with external
services. These don't fail and these
aren't slow. And I also get a database.
So instead of managing a separate
backend and a separate database, I'm
managing one infrastructure and that's
called convex. And what's cool about
convex is everything is real time. So
it's fast. I can read data from the
database. I can write data to my
database and I can interact with
external services. If you're familiar
with convex, these are basically called
queries, mutations, and actions, right?
Queries is querying data. Read.
Mutations is mutating data, right? and
actions is interacting with external
services. But here's another thing I
need to think about. When I'm building a
backend, what if, let's say, I'm
building a chat app and someone types a
message and they leave the chat app,
right? Is the chat going to continue or
is it going to fail? Now, if you build
the standard way, it will probably fail.
If you're vibe coding and you don't
understand how chat stream works and all
stuff, it will probably fail. I know
that I need durable processes. Now
again, you feel like I'm throwing all
these big words. I'm telling you, lock
in. This is easy. Durable processes. A
durable process is basically a process
that's durable, right? That continues to
go on. Even if you close the tab, close
the page, refresh, whatever it is, it
will continue to work. Now, if I didn't
have Convix, this is an additional thing
I have to build. Convix already builds
this. They call it workflow. I can set
up a workflow using their workflow
component. And if you don't know how to
set this up, literally if you have
convix, you go to convex components,
right? And you go search workflow and
you can literally copy paste this to
your agent. Simplify programming
longrunning code flows. Workflow
executes durably with configurable
retries and delays. So I need this
because I'm building an AI agent and the
AI agent can't stop working if people go
and leave. What if I wanted like a
lineup? Like let's say you're building
like a ticket master type site and
people are just hammering the site. You
have thousands of people using your site
and you want a queue, right? Again, with
back-end engineering, you would have to
build this yourself. But with convex,
this is available. I can have cues. I
can have coordinated parallel tasks,
which means I can have things run
parallelly. That's a hard word to say.
Parallel.
Parallel. You know what I'm trying to
say? Have bunch tasks run in parallel.
And I could do this. And they have a
component for this called workpool.
Right? Again, if I wanted a que, I can
use I believe it's Amazon AWS Q's. Is is
it called SQS, right? Amazon simple Q
service, right? So if I wanted a queue,
I would have to use this. If I wanted a
database, I would have to use RDS. If I
wanted virtual servers, I would use
this, right? So there's all these
different services. They're powerful,
but it's terrible user experience,
developer experience, agent experience.
Convex simplifies this, abstracts this,
and gives me one complete package. So, I
get all this and then on top of that, I
have my database. So, when it comes to
my backend and database, instead of
building these out separately, why don't
I use a service like Convex to do it? It
makes my life easier. Another pro to
Convex is everything is code. And the
reason why this is necessary and is
important is I want the agent to do the
work. I want the agent to build these
features on. I want the agent to do this
that and the third. And if the entire
backend is all code, if the database is
code, if everything is code, then the
agent can do those things for me. So
going back to Pluto, we have the client
surface, right? And then Pluto's control
plane, meaning the main orchestrator,
the main backend is Convex. Convex is
the source of truth. Convex is the
bridge. Convex handles everything and I
use Convex components. And again, here's
the thing. Another thing I love Convex
for and it just makes life easier is
integrations, right? And what do I mean
by integrations is let's say I wanted to
integrate Cloudflare's R2 storage. All I
do is search R2 and Convex has a
component for that. You know how I set
this up? I copy this link, give it to my
agent, and my agent set it up. Now I
have storage in my app and it's
connected to my back end. Now this seems
amazing, right? I have my client. I have
my backend and database. And that's it.
That's all to it. That's all Pluto is.
But hold on. There's a lot to Pluto. One
thing that Pluto has is services. And to
best explain a service, I'm going to use
AI. It says a service is a
self-contained reusable block of
software functionality that performs a
specific task for other parts of the
application or for external clients. So
there are two services in Pluto
inference/payments and iMessage. Let me
explain iMessage because it's easier. So
with Pluto one of the ways you can
communicate with your agent apart from
the internal chat or using telegram,
slack, discord soon is you can use
iMessage. You can talk with your agent
using iMessage. Now, um there's quite a
bit of work to it and it almost felt
like the iMessage code should live in
its own little contained box. Reason
being is it doesn't really mess with the
rest of the codebase. Like it doesn't
have that much of a foothold in many
different places and it feels like it's
better off being its own contained
thing. Now, this is a decision sort of
made off of experience/vibes
and it made sense for iMessage to be its
own contained thing. So, in my monor
repo, I can I'll remove UI and then I
can have iMessage here. This is its own
service. And then for
inference/payments,
again, this might be thinking a little
too ahead. I plan on Pluto having its
own inference system and the inference
is very tied and coupled with payments,
right? Again, people are able to fund
credits and these credits can be used
for inference and they use different
sort of models. This felt like a system
that should be on its own. A because the
convex backend started to get big. I
wanted to separate some things that
could be their own standalone service.
But second, God willing, if Pluto
succeeds and other developers are
working on it, I assume that there would
be a dedicated person solely working on
this, right? There would be a dedicated
person solely focused on this. Now, the
iMessage thing might be too small, but
again, it's literally its own thing, its
own box, and it makes sense to me for it
to be its own service. When we think of
services, I want us to think of a block
of code that can that touches one
surface area that does one specific
thing that doesn't really have a
foothold in the entire codebase, but can
be cleanly architected separately. I
think that makes sense to be a service.
Again, it's more experience and vibes
than it is a specific formula. So I
chose to make these two things separate
services. Now what stack did I use? Now
this may shock you. I used effect
TS and Postgress. Now I used effect TS
for the inference payments and
Postgress. For the iMessage it was just
effects. You might be asking me why
effect and the reason why I used effect
is a AI is actually very good with
writing effect code but b I needed
really strong error handling because if
things go wrong in inference and
payments I need to know about it. It
needs to be clean. It needs to be
architected and when it comes to error
handling nothing is as good as effect.
Right? So I use effect in the inference
service. I use effect in the iMessage
service and for the payment stuff it
there's it its own DB I have a postgress
database I'm using planet scale for this
but you can use any other provider and
this again also lives in the monor repo
so when I'm using whatever agent I'm
using that agent has access to all the
information and understands how the
system works again going back when you
think of how to set up your services
think about what things in your app that
you want to segment you also ask Fable
5, which is back this question. And for
payments, you might be wondering,
payments, what am I using again? There's
Stripe, there's Polar, there's Autumn.
Most of you probably be like, why don't
you you could just use Stripe. I wanted
to use Autumn because I have a credit
based system and the way my payments is
architected is uh very unique where
there's credits and there's things that
consume credits, there's things that are
free, there's things that you need to
top up and all this different stuff.
Like for example on Pluto, you can give
your agent a card and this card you
obviously need to give it money and you
can use your credits to top that up. So
that's something that Autumn takes care
of well. And what's cool again about
using Convex is Convex has an Autumn
component. So you know what I did? I
literally copied this and gave it to the
agent. So for payments, if it's just
direct straight up subscription, use
Stripe. If you have some credit based
stuff going on, I would use Autumn. Now,
you could already tell this is a pretty
large app. There's many places things
can go wrong, right? There's many places
in the client on the back end, the
different services. Heck, the monor
repo, you might be using Nex.js,
Tanstack star, you might whatever it is
that you're using. There's a lot of
places where this goes wrong. I
recommend checking out, and this is not
sponsored, Sentry and Post Hog. This is
what I use for analytics, error logging,
and all that type of stuff. You need to
have robust logging because you want to
make sure when something goes wrong,
when your app goes down, whatever it is,
when a build fails, whatever it is, you
want to make sure that you know exactly
what happened. And if you're a
non-technical person asking how do I do
this, you just tell AI, hey, I want to
make sure whenever an error happens, I
need to know how to track it. I need to
know when it happened. Use sentry and
post talk to make this happen. The
system architecture diagram drawn by
cursor agent. um explain about con
explain convex control plane to you
explain how I use components uh we have
the inference ledger system right this
is again built with effect we have a
postgress wallet ledger we're using open
router as the underlying you know
inference provider and I'm obviously
using open claw the agent openclaw is
being deployed on Daytona I need Daytona
because Daytona is a great sandbox
provider and not only do I get sandbox
with Daytona but every agent also
gets a computer, right? So, right here,
you're going to see that my very own
Pluto agent has its own computer with a
browser. I asked it to take a screenshot
and believe it or not, something broke.
It selfhealed and then it sent me the
screenshot. Right? So, this is something
I can't build myself. Again, I need an
abstraction layer that makes it easy.
Daytona is great. And then for OOTH, I'm
using work OS. And the reason why I'm
using work OS is for one simple main
reason. First and foremost, it's uh
pretty good. And second of all, it's
enterprise ready, right? Pluto, I'm not
really targeting personal agent people.
I really want to go for businesses, you
know, small to medium, like 15 to like
60 employees. Manager sets it up,
invites people. Work OS makes the OOTH
for like companies and if there's a
specific compliance that I need, it
makes it really, really easy. and the
agents love it, so I'm using it. Now,
when I look at this system that I've
designed for Pluto, what are some of the
trade-offs I made? The first one is
cost. I don't know how this business is
going to make money. Like, I more so
want people to try it out and really
like it and that's a problem for later.
So, that's the one thing I have not like
thought of like cost optimizations, this
this that and the third. I just want to
make sure when people use the app, it
doesn't break. Even like the Daytona
boxes that we're using are, you know,
medium to large size boxes. I want to
make sure everyone's agent is fast. You
know, work OS has a pretty generous free
tier. So does Convex. And then like
again, I have a separate service. Like
if I wanted to save money, I would just
literally put everything in Convex, but
I have a separate service. Um I'm using
Versell for deployments and I can
actually show you that. and with Versel.
So I have Pluto, I have a staging
environment, I have the inference uh
service, I have an admin site, you know,
all these like are like deploying these
and shipping changes like you can see
I'm on the $20 a month plan, but I've
spent over $100 so far. So cost is the
one thing where I'm like, you know what,
we ball. So this is why I think it's
very important when you're building your
app out to think about this, right? to
architect it in a way where adding new
features and tools and stuff won't break
your app. This is why I always start
with a monor repo, right? One repo that
can have multiple different things. A
web app, a mobile app, a desktop app,
one unified backend, many backends, many
services, whatever it is, right? Cuz the
agent has everything in one repo, has
access to all the code. And then even
the tools I use are tools that the
agents are very familiar with and know
how to use. Versel, excellent, right?
Excellent place to deploy. Uh, Convex,
excellent. Everything is code. The
agents love it. Payments, Autumn. Autumn
is really pretty good. Like I, again,
because I'm using Convex, there's tools
that maybe the agent might not be good
at using the tool specifically, but it's
good at using the Convex component. So,
the Convex component helps me integrate
tools that I like, like Autumn, like
Reset, like Stripe, like whatever it is.
I literally just go to Convex components
and then I search it. And because this
is how I start my applications now
adding on services, segmenting specific
things. It's not difficult. The agent
itself can do it. And every tool I'm
using can handle scale. Versel can
handle scale. Convex can handle scale.
Autumn can handle scale. You know, all
these tools that I'm using are tried and
true. A lot of people use them. A lot of
successful companies use them. And for
the most part, there's not like like
increasing like let's say a thousand
users join in the app. The only thing
that I need to do for the most part is
up my subscription and then I can use AI
to sort of optimize the app. There's not
going to be a reason why the app goes
down because I built it on solid infra
unless there's bad code, but we're
talking about system design here. That's
pretty much it. This video is pretty
long. I hope you enjoyed it. I hope you
enjoy me talking about the decisions and
and the design and the way I'm building
things. Again, I'm not saying this is
the greatest way to do so, but this is
how I'm thinking about apps. This is how
I build apps at my agency, Hey Fabrica.
And I hope this makes sense. I hope you
enjoyed it. Make sure to like, comment,
subscribe. Let me know if you want to
watch more videos like this. I'll cook
them up for you. But as always, you've
been awesome. My name is Ross. I'll see
you in the next one. Peace.